Guide to the Advocate Research and Education Foundation/Advocate Experience Records, 1978-1981
Advocate Research and Education Foundation/Advocate Experience Records, 1978-1981
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Advocate Research and Education Foundation/Advocate Experience records, 1978-1981
7310
Advocate Research and Education Foundation
12.5 cubic ft.
Correspondence, financial records, registration files, topical seminar background material, "facilitator information sheets," audio and video cassettes, slides.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection pertains chiefly to the Advocate Experience, an EST-derived seminar for lesbians and gays founded by David B. Goodstein. The contains various materials from 1978 to 1981 of the Advocate Research and Education Foundation Board and the Advocate Experience staff, and manuals pertaining to the Advocate Experience and the Outrageous Experience (a seminar for instructors).
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
In the 1970s, David B. Goodstein created the Advocate Research and Education Foundation, a non-profit structure through which to conduct the "Advocate Experience." Initially the Experience was a one-weekend seminar similar to Werner Erhard's EST, only targeted at a gay audience. The foundation was eventually combined with the Mariposa Education and Research Foundation.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection is divided into four series: Advocate Research and Education Foundation and Advocate Experience Correspondence and Memos' and Alphabetical Subject File; Facilitator Information Sheets; and an Audio and Video cassette series. The Facilitator Information Sheets are restricted until 2041.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Goodstein, David B., 1932-1985.
Subjects:
Homosexuality.; Gay men.; Gays.; Psychotherapy.; Erhard seminar training.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Boxes ten, eleven, and twelve (10, 11, 12) are restricted until 2041.
RELATED MATERIAL
David B. Goodstein papers, #7311.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Correspondence (incoming and outgoing)
Boxes 1-4
Series II. Alphabetical Subject File
Boxes 5-9
Series III. Advocate Experience Facilitator Information Sheets [ RESTRICTED]
Boxes 10-12
Series IV. Advocate Experience Audio and Video Cassettes and Slides
Box 13
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Correspondence (incoming and outgoing)
  - 1978 Advocate Research and Education Foundation Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
  - 1978 Advocate Experience Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 5-12)
    - A (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - B (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - C (Box 1, Folder 15-17)
    - D (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
    - E (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - F (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - G (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - G-H (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - H-J (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - J-K (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - K-L (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - M (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - M-O (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - P-R (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - R (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - R-S (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - S-T (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - T-V (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - W-Z (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 1979 Advocate Research and Education Foundation Correspondence
    - January (Box 1, Folder 35-37)
    - February (Box 1, Folder 38-43)
    - March (Box 1, Folder 44-47)
    - April (Box 2, Folder 1-5)
    - May (Box 2, Folder 6-8)
    - June (Box 2, Folder 9-11)
    - July (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
    - August (Box 2, Folder 14-17)
    - September (Box 2, Folder 18-21)
    - October (Box 2, Folder 22-26)
    - November (Box 2, Folder 27-30)
    - December (Box 2, Folder 31-36)
    - A-Z Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 37-39)
  - 1979 Advocate Experience Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 40-48)
  - 1980 Advocate Experience Correspondence
    - A (Box 2, Folder 49-50)
    - B (Box 2, Folder 51-53)
    - B (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - C (Box 3, Folder 2-6)
    - D (Box 3, Folder 7-11)
    - E (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - E-F (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - F (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
    - G (Box 3, Folder 16-19)
    - H (Box 3, Folder 20-22)
    - I (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - J (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - K (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - L (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
    - M (Box 3, Folder 28-32)
    - M-N (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - O (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - P (Box 3, Folder 35-37)
    - P-R (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - R (Box 3, Folder 39-40)
    - S (Box 3, Folder 41-45)
    - T (Box 3, Folder 46-47)
    - T-V (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - W (Box 3, Folder 49-51)
    - W-Z (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1980 Advocate Research and Education Foundation Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
  - 1981 Advocate Research and Education Foundation and Advocate Experience Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 4-10)
  - 1979-81 Advocate Research and Education Foundation and Advocate Experience Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 11-17)
  - David B. Goodstein Correspondence, 1979-81 (Box 4, Folder 18-23)
  - 1979-80 Advocate Research and Education Foundation and Advocate Experience Memo File (Box 4, Folder 24-38)
    - Incoming Memos (Box 4, Folder 39-44)
    - 1980 Advocate Research and Education Foundation and Advocate Experience Outgoing Memos (Box 4, Folder 45-46)
    - Selected Financial Records, Advocate Research and Education Foundation and Advocate Experience, 1978-80 (Box 4, Folder 47-56)
- Series II. Alphabetical Subject File
  - Agreements
    - Apprentice Agreements (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Seminar Agreements (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Houston Agreements (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Leadership Experience Handout Agreements (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco Agreements (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Ambassador's Test - Sacramento (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Articles of Incorporation (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Assignments (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Assistants' Orientation (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - David B. Goodstein's notes on Assisting (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Audio Visual (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors, Advocate Research and Education Fund (AREF)
    - Responses (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Proposed Agenda Items (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Executive Committee Memos (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - St. Paul Survey Result 30 Aug. 1978 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - St. Paul Survey Opinion Survey, 27 April 1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - 27 June 1978 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - 18 Sept. 1978 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - 18 Oct. 1978 Outrageous Experience (OX) Memo (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - 8 Nov. 1978 Funding and Playboy Foundation Response (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - 11 Dec. 1978 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - 1978 Miscellaneous Minutes (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - 22 Jan. 1979 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - 5 March 1979 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 24-25)
    - 2 May 1979 Interim Report (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - 17 June 1979 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - 14 Aug. 1979 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - 13 Sept. 1979 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 29-31)
    - 28 Dec. 1979 Executive Director's Report (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - 1979 Miscellaneous Minutes (Box 5, Folder 33-34)
    - 5 Jan. 1980 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - 15 Jan. 1980 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - 9 May 1980 Memo. (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - 20 June 1980 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - 5 Aug. 1980 Special Meeting (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - 20 Oct. 1980 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 40-41)
    - 1980 Miscellaneous Minutes and Memos (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - 7 April 1981 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 43-44)
    - 30 June 1981 Meeting and Executive Director's Report 22 June 1981 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - 4 Aug. 1981 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - 18 Dec. 1981 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 47-48)
    - Miscellaneous Minutes (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - 11 June 1982 Meeting (Box 5, Folder 50-51)
  - Brochure Consent Forms (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Budget
    - 1 Feb. 1979 - 31 Jan. 1980 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - 1980 Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 54-56)
    - Notes (Box 5, Folder 57-58)
    - Historical Plan (Box 5, Folder 59-60)
    - Advocate Game (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Calendar (Box 5, Folder 62-63)
  - Career Course Development (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Advocate Research and Education Fund (AREF) Cash Position (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Cash Flow Statements and Summaries (Box 5, Folder 66-68)
  - Charge Authorization and Charge Slip Preparation (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Check Information
    - Advocate Research and Education Fund (AREF) Check Registers (Box 5, Folder 70-71)
    - Bad Checks (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Pending Bounced Checks (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Confirmation Pack (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Corporate Documents (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Corporate Resolutions (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence - Advocate Experience (AX) Broadsides, Calendars, Invitations, Letters, Promotional Material (Box 5, Folder 77-79)
  - Creation Materials - Advocate Gay Experience and Advocate Game, a.k.a. Project "Pouf" 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 80-83)
    - Includes Board Memos, Marketing Plans, Brochures, Manuals and Handwritten Notes (Box 6, Folder 1-16)
  - Dade County Study 1978 - Public Response Associates (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Data Project (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Denver Nov. 1981 - Advocate Experience (AX) Registration Diary (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Diary Forms (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Donations (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Enrollment Revenue Summaries (Box 6, Folder 22-24)
  - Facilitator - Apprentice Meeting 14 April 1979 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Advocate Experience For Family and Friends (AXFF) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Fantasies - Durk Dehner - Advocate Experience (AX) Graduate Event (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Advocate Research and Education Fund (AREF) Film Project (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Financial Statements (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - First Four Minutes (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Fundraising (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Furniture and Fixtures (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Futuresex (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Gay Day Parade (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Goodwat Advertising (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Graduates - Advocate Experience (AX) "Preview" (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Graduate Records System (Box 6, Folder 37-38)
    - Graduate Records System - Diversified Computer Applications (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Graduate Seminars (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Graduate Seminar Campaign Plan (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Graduate Support (Box 6, Folder 42-43)
  - Graduation (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Graphics Team (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Graphic Typesetting (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Guest Experience (Box 6, Folder 47-48)
  - Hawaii
    - 1979 - Miscellaneous Organizational Materials (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - 1980 - Miscellaneous Organizational Materials (Box 6, Folder 50-51)
    - Jan. 1982 - Advocate Experience (AX) Registration Diary (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - The Heterosexual Experience (Box 6, Folder 53-55)
  - Holiday Outreach To The Aging (HOTTA) (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - 1979 - New York (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - 1979 - San Francisco (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Human Sexual Enrichment Series (Box 6, Folder 59-61)
  - Advocate Research and Education Fund (AREF) - General Information (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - In Home Guest Event (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - In Service Checks (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Insurance Coverage (Box 6, Folder 65-68)
  - Integrity Seminar (Box 6, Folder 69-70)
  - Integrity Tone Scale (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Inventory System (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Invitation Letters (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Leadership Experience Handout - Assertive vs. Aggressive (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Leadership Experience Handout - Problem Solving (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Leadership Mastery Workshop - Innovation Associates (Box 6, Folder 76-78)
  - Central Office Lease - 5670 Wilshire Blvd., Los Angeles, CA (Box 6, Folder 79-81)
  - Lease - 550 Larchmont Ave., Los Angeles, CA (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Lease - 232 E. 35th St., New York, NY (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Life Experience Miscellaneous Drafts and Notes (Box 7, Folder 1-5)
  - Lifespring (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Lighten Your Lurk, Edward Dunn 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles
    - Oct. 1981 - Advocate Experience (AX) Registration Diary (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Dec. 1981 - Advocate Experience (AX) Registration Diary (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Jan. 1981 - Advocate Experience (AX) Registration Diary (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Making Relationships Work - Notes (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Management Group List (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Manatt, Phelps, Rothenberg and Tunney (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Manuals
    - Center Management Functions March 1979 (Box 7, Folder 14-16)
    - Center Management Functions Changes (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Manual Changes (Box 7, Folder 18-20)
    - Manual Distribution (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Enrollment Team (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Facilitators', Advocate Experience (AX) Weekend March 1978 (Box 7, Folder 23-25)
    - Facilitators', Advocate Experience (AX) Weekend May 1980 (Box 7, Folder 26-28)
    - Facilitators', Advocate Experience (AX) Weekend Nov. 1980 (Box 7, Folder 29-31)
    - Facilitators', Advocate Experience (AX) II Weekend Sept. 1980 (Box 7, Folder 32-33)
    - Facilitators', Advocate Experience (AX) Weekend n.d. (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Family and Friends Training Nov. 1978 (Box 7, Folder 35-36)
    - General Assistant Day Oct. 1979 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Graduate Support Team June 1980 (Box 7, Folder 38-39)
    - Graduate Support Telephone Team Nov. 1979 (Box 7, Folder 40-41)
    - Guest Team Training March 1980 (Box 7, Folder 42-43)
    - Guest Telephone Team Nov. 1979 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Intensive Facilitators' Aug. 1981 (Box 7, Folder 45-46)
    - Life Experience (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Librarian's May 1980 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Logistics, Advocate Experience (AX) II Nov. 1979 (Box 7, Folder 49-50)
    - Opening Space For Satisfying Relationships - Facilitators' April 1980 (Box 7, Folder 51-52)
    - Physical Aliveness Seminar - Logistics (Box 7, Folder 53-57)
    - Post-Experience Logistics June 1978 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Presenters Program May 1980 (Box 7, Folder 59-60)
    - Team Orientation (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Team Training (Box 7, Folder 62-63)
  - Mariposa Foundation (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Marketing Plan (Box 7, Folder 65-67)
  - Media - Articles and Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Media Person's Guide To The Advocate Experience (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Incoming Memos, 6380 Wilshire Blvd., Los Angeles, CA (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Statistical Report Memos Sent To Centers (Box 7, Folder 71-73)
  - Monogamy (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Notes on New Research (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - New York Bookings (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Office Duties and Forms (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Office Projects (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "Opening Space" (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "Opening Space" Logistics (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Originals (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Outrageous Experience (OX)
    - Miscellaneous Drafts, Creation Materials, Organizational Information (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Original Drafts of Manual (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
    - Caldwell Williams Correspondence and Agreements (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Organizational Lists and Memos - New York May 1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Organizational Lists and Memos - California June 1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Organizational Lists - California Sept. 1979 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Participants Lists, Memos, Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence to Participants 1978 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence to Participants 1979 (Box 8, Folder 18-19)
  - Participants List (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Los Angeles Party (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - San Francisco Party (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Payroll Record (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Advocate Research and Education Fund (AREF) Payroll
    - Payroll - 1981 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Payroll Taxes (Box 8, Folder 25-26)
    - Payroll Taxes - California (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Personnel Records (Box 8, Folder 28-31)
  - Personnel Policies (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - P.O.E.M. (Plan, Organize, Execute, Manage)
    - Advocate Experience (AX) Graduate Event Planning Drafts (Box 8, Folder 33-34)
    - New York Agreement Dec. 1980 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Los Angeles Agreement Oct. 1980 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Los Angeles Weekend March 1980 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Los Angeles Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - New York Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Political B.S. (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Advocate Experience Presenters Program (AXPP)
    - Informational Brochures, Correspondence, and Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Training (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Profit and Loss Statements (Box 8, Folder 43-46)
  - Proposed Procedures (Box 8, Folder 47-48)
  - Public Response Associates (PRA)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Drafts (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - St. Paul Opinion Survey (Box 8, Folder 50-57)
    - Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Relationships Course (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Reports - New York Office (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Reports - San Francisco Office (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - San Francisco Broadsides (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - San Francisco Intensive Nov. 1981 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Scholarship Applications (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Daily Statistical Sheets (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Stor Dor Freight System (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Taking the Bullshit Out of Politics (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Taking Responsibility For Your Own Life (Box 8, Folder 68-72)
  - Targets (Box 8, Folder 73-74)
  - Tax Information
    - Tax Returns 31 Jan. 1979 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Tax Returns 31 Jan. 1980 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Federal Taxes (Box 8, Folder 77-78)
    - New York Taxes (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Tax Exempt Applications (Box 9, Folder 1-6)
  - Training (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Transparencies
    - AX Experience (Box 9, Folder 8-13)
    - AXII Experience (Box 9, Folder 14-15)
    - Post Experience (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Taking Responsibility For Your Own Life (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Union Bank (Box 9, Folder 18-19)
  - Advocate Experience Statistics (Box 9, Folder 20-22)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Guest Cards (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) August 1978 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Los Angeles Weekly Reports 1979 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - San Francisco Weekly Reports 1979 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Opening Space for Satisfying Relationships, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Physical Aliveness II, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) May 1978 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) June 1979 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Houston 1981 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) August 1981, Denver (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Statistics, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - New York Weekly Reports, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - September Experience, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 35-37)
  - July Experience, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Outrageous Experience, New York, May 1980 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - November Experience, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 40-42)
  - Advocate Experience Office Memos, Lists, etc. (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Series III. Advocate Experience Facilitator Information Sheets [ RESTRICTED]
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Denver - 29-30 Jan. 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Denver - 14-15 Nov. 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 4-6)
  - Advocate Experience Intensive Houston - 1 Sept. 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 7-9)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Houston - 1 Sept. 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 10-12)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 10-11 March 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 17-18 March 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 15-17)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 12-13 May 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 18-20)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 16-17 June 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 21-23)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 28-29 July 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 24-26)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 8-9 Sept 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 27-29)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 13-14 Oct. 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 17-18 Nov. 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 31-32)
  - Outrageous Experience (OX) New York - 22-25 Nov. 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 33-34)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 15-16 Dec. 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 26-27 Jan. 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 36-38)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 8-9 March 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 39-40)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 19-20 April 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 41-42)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 31 May - 1 June 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 43-44)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 12-13 July 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 45-46)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 6-7 Sept. 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 47-48)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 18-19 Oct. 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 49-50)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 22-23 Nov. 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 51-52)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 7-8 March 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 13-14 June 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) New York - 17-18 Oct. 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 6-7 May 1978 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 3-4 June 1978 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 8-9 July 1978 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 9-10)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 12-13 Aug. 1978 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 11-12)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 16-17 Sept. 1978 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 13-14)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 4-5 Nov. 1978 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 15-17)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 6-7 Jan. 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 18-20)
  - Advocate Experience for Family and Friends (AXFF) Los Angeles - 6-7 Jan. 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 10-11 Feb. 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 22-24)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 24-25 March 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 25-26)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 5-6 May 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 27-28)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 9-10 June 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 29-30)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 14-15 July 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 31-32)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 11-12 Aug. 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 33-34)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 15-16 September 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 35-36)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 13-14 Oct. 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 10-11 Nov. 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 38-39)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 8-9 Dec. 1979 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 40-41)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 12-13 Jan. 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 42-43)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 1-2 March 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 44-46)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 12-13 April 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 47-48)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 17-18 May 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 28-29 June 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 2-4)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 9-10 Aug. 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 13-14 Sept. 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 25-26 Oct. 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 9-10)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 6-7 Dec. 1980 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 11-12)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 17-18 Jan. 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 13-14)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 28 Feb. - 1 Mar. 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 15-16)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 11-12 Apr. 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 17-18)
  - Advocate Experience (AX) Los Angeles - 16-17 May 1981 [ RESTRICTED] (Box 12, Folder 19)